KRISTER BRITHANNY MUNGUÍA CHAVEZ

Software Developer

9	Res.	Lomas	de	las	Cascada	ıs, Cl	holoma
---	------	-------	----	-----	---------	--------	--------

- kbmchavez@outlook.com
- □ https://kristerch65.github.io/

- in krister-munguia-5292511a8
- +504 9644-1120
- github.com/KristerCh65

25 years old

- m May 6 1999
- D 0501-2001-03929

PROFILE INFO

Passionate developer with experience in infrastructure management and application development using various technologies and frameworks. Specialized in the administration of platforms such as ServiceNow and with solid skills in programming languages such as C#, Java, and JavaScript. I seek to contribute my technical knowledge and analytical skills to a dynamic and growing team.

EXPERIENCE

2023 - PRESENT

Altiatek LLC. | Altia Business Park, SPS

Technical Consultant

- Develop and execute comprehensive strategies and solutions that align with the needs and objectives of the company.
- Remote customer service and maintenance and management of a highperformance team, promoting a collaborative and results-oriented work environment.
- Create, manage and implement solutions or integrations according to needs assessment, ensuring efficient allocation of resources and optimizing it.
- ServiceNow platform administration, reports, business rules, client-scripts (with AngularJS and Javascript).

2021 - 2023

Feyco Hardware Store I Bo. Medina, SPS

IT Manager

- Provide good service and attention to internal customers, troubleshooting problems with Hardware and Software.
- Maintenance and management of equipment and network infrastructure, such as Windows servers, Fortinet, contracts, licenses and integration projects.
- Create and manage the IT budget, ensuring efficient allocation of resources and optimizing ROI.
- Monitor IT technologies to identify customer needs and strategies to resolve pain points in the business and provide better infrastructure.

KEY PROJECTS -

- Implementing Lynx HR management platform 2022
- BeeTrack for Logistic Tracking, reduce rute gaps 2023

REFERENCES

Ing. Allan Lopez

Puzzle / CFO

Phone: +504 9623-4196 Email: allan@puzzle.tech

Ing. Alexander Villalvir

Sr Full Stack Dev / Stepstone

Phone: +504 3336-2013 Email: javc1603@gmail.com

EDUCATION

2024 | Junior Achivement

Cloud Computing

Web Development + Cloud Computing: Cloud Practitioner Certification - AWS

2017 - 2022 | CEUTEC

Computer Engineering

Develop and manage computer systems, applications and technological solutions.

SKILLS

- Project Management
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Effective Communication
- Critical Thinking

TECH SKILLS

- Programming Languages:
 - C#, PHP, HTML, SQL, Java, JavaScript, CSS
- Frameworks:
 - Angular, React, Flutter
- Platform Administration:
 - ServiceNow, IIS, FileServer, Active Directory
- Databases:
 - SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, FireBase

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (native)
- English (intermediate)